<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation Guide on Crunchy Data Container Suite Documentation</title>
    <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/latest/installation-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation Guide on Crunchy Data Container Suite Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/latest/installation-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation Guide</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/latest/installation-guide/installation-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/latest/installation-guide/installation-guide/</guid>
      <description>Requirements These installation instructions are developed and tested for the following operating systems:
 CentOS 7
 RHEL 7
  The Crunchy Container Suite can run on different environments including:
 Docker 1.13+
 OpenShift Container Platform 3.11
 Kubernetes 1.8+
  In this document we list the basic installation steps required for these environments.
Project Environment If your goal is to simply run the containers any properly configured user account should work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storage Configuration</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/latest/installation-guide/storage-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/latest/installation-guide/storage-configuration/</guid>
      <description>Storage Configuration Available Storage Types The Crunchy Container Suite is officially tested using two different storage backends:
 HostPath (single node testing) NFS (single and multi-node testing)  Other storage backends work as well, including GCE, EBS, ScaleIO, and others, but may require you to modify various examples or configuration.
The Crunchy Container Suite is tested, developed, and examples are provided that use the various storage types listed above. This ensures that customers have a high degree of choices when it comes to choosing a volume type.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>