<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributing on Crunchy Data Container Suite Documentation</title>
    <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributing on Crunchy Data Container Suite Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building the Containers</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/building/</guid>
      <description>Build From Source There are many cases where you may want to build the containers from source, such as working on a patch to contribute a feature. This guide provides the instructions to get you set up to build from source.
Requirements  CentOS 7 or Red Hat 7 environment. The instructions below are set up for CentOS 7, but you can read the installation guide for additional instructions go version 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submitting Issues</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/issues/</guid>
      <description>If you would like to submit an feature / issue for us to consider please submit an issue to the official GitHub Repository.
If you would like to work any current or open issues, please update the issue with your efforts so that we can avoid redundant or unnecessary work.
If you have any questions, you can submit a Support - Question and Answer issue and we will work with you on how you can get more involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submitting Pull Requests</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/pull-requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/pull-requests/</guid>
      <description>So you decided to submit an issue and work it. Great! Let&amp;rsquo;s get it merged in to the codebase. The following will go a long way to helping get the fix merged in quicker:
 Fork the Github repository and make a branch off of the master branch Create a Pull Request from your Fork back to the master branch. Update the checklists in the Pull Request description. Reference which issues this Pull Request is resolving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/documentation-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/crunchy-containers/4.6.8/contributing/documentation-updates/</guid>
      <description>The documentation website is generated using Hugo.
Hosting Hugo Locally (Optional) If you would like to build the documentation locally, view the official Installing Hugo guide to set up Hugo locally.
The git submodule for the crunchy-hugo-theme has to be synched -
cd $CCPROOT/ git submodule init git submodule update You can then start the server by running the following commands -
cd $CCPROOT/docs/ hugo server The local version of the Hugo server is accessible by default from localhost:1313.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>